还威胁到了我国的传统价值观"
It threatens the traditional values of this country."
沃尔先生  同性婚姻
Mr. Wall, how does gay marriage
怎么就威胁到桑托勒姆先生的婚姻了
threaten Mr. Santorum's marriage?
参议员认为婚姻
The senator believes that marriage
应当是一男一女的结合
is defined as the union of one man and one woman.
我明白前参议员是这么认为的
I understand that's what the former senator believes.
但他说的是
But what he said was that
同性婚姻威胁到了他的乃至所有人的婚姻
gay marriages threatens his marriage and all marriages.
我问的正是  这威胁从何而来
And I'm asking you exactly how it's a threat.
对里克·桑托勒姆而言
Sanctity of life is the number one issue
生命的神圣是头等大事  他认为...
with Rick Santorum, and he believes...
沃尔先生  请不要用"神圣"这种模糊的词
Mr. Wall, we'll get to purposely vague words like sanctity in a moment.
请你正面回答我的问题
But I'd like you to try to answer the question.
桑托勒姆先生的婚姻
How is Mr. Santorum's marriage threatened